A good morning my dear friends
welcome to dance middle school
friends and
we will cover all the important current affairs in this video
so subscribe friends this is
celebrated in depth of Raghavan do not forget to
subscribe about the appointment of national on
Thursday also subscribe subscribe
like one of our friends
international appointment if any
question comes in the team
which day was celebrated on 3rd May friends
subscribe it was in Netherlands Netherlands
friends apart from this friends a special
migratory bird day is celebrated
subscribe
and one of the topics this disease is celebrated is that
today's second question is which country's
cricket circular subscribe
which country's mark was appointed subscribe that
in Pakistan subscribe
subscribe Bluetooth
appointment subscribe subscribe
in to chicken let's move ahead
MP4
that after whom in Israel a road was named the
festival which country that talk about any
great man's youth so friends Rabindranath
Tagore Rabindranath Tagore appointed
subscribe
airplane mode Jain
which bank has been charged with Sanjivani
Health Research  The accused
Sunil health insurance policy was launched by the bank
subscribe the accused appointed by it
subscribe when was it nationalized in Mumbai Maharashtra
1969 subscribe subscribe subscribe
subscribe
Maharashtra Maharashtra loot number
on this number governor okay friends and
similarly the CEO of ICICI Bank
subscribe Maharashtra Punjab school okay
friends now
that the first Hindu pilot to join the Pakistan Air Force
friends
Rahul Dev became the first officer
pilot to join the Pakistan Air Force Rahul is
difficult Imran Khan's Pakistan
and Pakistan and India best friend
you know this happened so let's see
when is Mother's Day i.e. Mother's Day celebrated
so friends subscribe and
friends subscribe makes the appointment of 11 nations that which has been
in the news recently that the
password of gambling is PET it has been
in the news and what is this so friends this is
America's anti-missile system American
middle aged subscribe friends which
state has started the Nikah scheme
which state has started the Nikah scheme and
this scheme has been started in Himachal Pradesh that
about Himachal Pradesh the state's
appointment of Jairam Thakur and till this is
appointed the Governor of Maharashtra located and
subscribe  In Uttar Pradesh, the appointment of Uttar Pradesh
Lucknow from Anand, the team here has been
formed, appointed by the UP government and
subscribe also, the UP government will come but
when the scooter runs away, to
fight the gas plant and to
start the work Madhav Seva, do
subscribe to the channel, it is located in subscribe,
okay, friends, who is the Chief Minister of Madhya Pradesh,
Yogi Adityanath and who is the Governor,
Anandiben Patel, in this way let's
see about Madhya Pradesh,
friends, that is the ghee of Madhya Pradesh, subscribe and
who is the Governor, subscribe, apart from this, the
appointment of subscribe to Madhya Pradesh, oh okay,
friends, similarly let's
see about Gujarat, once the problem of Gujarat,
Gandhinagar, Gandhinagar,
who is the minister, subscribe
and friends, as the Chief Minister of Gujarat,
subscribe and subscribe, the appointment
of subscribe and this committee does that
I come out of the place of worship,
okay, friends, Rail Gandhinagar,
who is the richest person of India, through
subscribe,
do tell this appointment and if you want to share it with your friends, then
friends, we will meet in the next video, till then,
bye-bye, thank you